How to replace a tag
How to replace fast tag on any vehicle number First go to the
search bar then select the tag account then enter the
license plate number i.e. enter the
vehicle number I have
typed the vehicle
number here and after entering the vehicle number I have to search the
vehicle details have come up now the current
balance
is sufficient here so I have to go to manage account then go to
manage tag then
select the manage option here it is
assigned in the status
it has to be returned damaged I am showing the last
but after returning the tag send to customer
OTP will go to the customer after taking the OTP it has to be
submitted here OTP verified then
update it there
after updating it go to manage account
then select the manage vehicle option then go to
request tag after selecting the request tag then
go to manage account and go to assign tag
send OTP to customer then
OTP will go to the customer then OTP has to be collected and
submitted here then
select the select option and tax serial  You have to
enter the number and assign it, that's all, this was the
replacement
process, thank you
everyone.